<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nebula</string>
    <string name="dark_mode">Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="zodiac_intro">Let\'s, find out your zodiac sign!</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="date_invalid">Date cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="month_invalid">Month cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="zodiac_results_x">%1$s</string>
    <string name="year_invalid">Year cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="zodiac_results">Your zodiac here!</string>
    <string name="zodiac_image">Zodiac Image</string>
    <string name="see_details">See Details</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="share_template">Date\t\t: %1$s\nMonth\t: %2$s\nYear\t\t: %3$s\n\n%4$s</string>
    <string name="no_data_yet">No Data Yet</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="delete_history">Delete History</string>

    //Details title
    <string name="title_aquarius">The Water Bearers</string>
    <string name="title_pisces">The Fishes</string>
    <string name="title_aries">The Rams</string>
    <string name="title_taurus">The Bulls</string>
    <string name="title_gemini">The Twins</string>
    <string name="title_cancer">The Crabs</string>
    <string name="title_leo">The Lions</string>
    <string name="title_virgo">The Virgins</string>
    <string name="title_libra">The Scales</string>
    <string name="title_scorpio">The Scorpions</string>
    <string name="title_sagittarius">The Archers</string>
    <string name="title_capricorn">The Goats</string>
    <string name="title_invalid">PeekaBoo!</string>

    //Detailed content
    <string name="details_aquarius">Aquarius is an innovative, independent, and idealistic zodiac sign.
        They often have unique and forward-thinking perspectives. Aquarius also cares about social
        issues and has a passion for making the world a better place.</string>
    <string name="details_pisces">Pisces is an intuitive, sensitive, and empathetic zodiac sign.
        They have a strong imagination and often feel connected to the spiritual world. Pisces is
        also artistic, compassionate, and deeply attuned to the emotions of others.</string>
    <string name="details_aries">Aries is an energetic, enthusiastic, and courageous zodiac sign.
        They possess strong leadership qualities and often have a great drive to achieve their goals.
        Aries also tend to be daring risk-takers and have a adventurous spirit.</string>
    <string name="details_taurus">Taurus is known as a practical, stable, and resilient zodiac sign.
        They highly value comfort and beauty and often have an interest in art and material possessions.
        Taurus is also loyal and steadfast in relationships.</string>
    <string name="details_gemini">Gemini is an intelligent, communicative, and highly social zodiac sign.
        They have a tendency to adapt quickly and have diverse interests.
        Gemini is also renowned for being articulate and easygoing.</string>
    <string name="details_cancer">Cancer is an emotional, caring, and compassionate zodiac sign.
        They form strong bonds with family and home and often exhibit a high sensitivity towards the feelings of others.
        Cancer also tends to protect and nurture their loved ones.</string>
    <string name="details_leo">Leo is a confident, brave, and enthusiastic zodiac sign.
        They often stand out and have a need for recognition and appreciation.
        Leo also tends to be a charismatic leader and radiates warmth and excitement.</string>
    <string name="details_virgo">Virgo is a practical, analytical, and detail-oriented zodiac sign.
        They have high standards for themselves and others and often become perfectionists.
        Virgo also focuses on details and possesses strong analytical abilities.</string>
    <string name="details_libra">Libra is a harmonious, fair, and social zodiac sign.
        They have a tendency to seek balance and harmony in relationships and their environment.
        Libra also has an affinity for beauty and an interest in art and aesthetics.</string>
    <string name="details_scorpio">Scorpio is a passionate, mysterious, and sharp zodiac sign.
        They have intense energy and often possess strong emotional strength.
        Scorpio is also known for their loyalty and sharp instincts in reading others.</string>
    <string name="details_sagittarius">Sagittarius is an adventurous, free-spirited, and optimistic zodiac sign.
        They have a high spirit for exploring the world and seeking new experiences.
        Sagittarius is also honest, open-minded, and has a broad and optimistic view of life.</string>
    <string name="details_capricorn">Capricorn is an ambitious, practical, and serious zodiac sign.
        They have clear goals and the perseverance to achieve them. Capricorn is also tough, responsible, and reliable.</string>
    <string name="details_invalid">Your birth date has not been created yet, maybe in the future there will be one, who knows!</string>

    //AboutApp
    <string name="about_application">About Application</string>
    <string name="copyright">Nebula is an Android application for
        search for the name of the zodiac so that someone can know the zodiac and knowledge about the
        zodiac.\n\nThis application is made for classes Assessment Mobpro 1. Find the code at
        https://github.com/rifanmuhammadhidayat/Nebula.git\n\nCopyright © 2023 Rifan Muhammad Hidayat.\nAll rights reserved.</string>

    //History
    <string name="data_x">Date: %1$d - Month: %2$d</string>
    <string name="results_x">%1$s</string>

    //Delete
    <string name="delete_button">Delete</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_history">Delete History?</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_all_history">Delete All History?</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="switch_layout">Ubah tampilan</string>
</resources>